<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ClearSky</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tabs">TabsActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tab 3</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_map">Map</string>
    <string name="title_pollutants">Pollutants</string>

    <!-- Sliders -->
    <string-array name="slide_titles">
        <item><![CDATA[<h2>Welcome to ClearSky !</h2>]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[<h2>Setting up the Raspberry Pi</h2>]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[<h2>Setting up the sensors</h2>]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[<h2>Setting up ClearSky</h2>]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[<h2>Addresses</h2>]]></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="slide_content">
        <item><![CDATA[
             <p>With the next few pages we’ll try and help you setup your mliti-pollutions sensing system.</p>
             <p>Depending on your familiarity with the Raspberry Pi, the process may take up to 15 minutes.</p>
        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[
            <p>First up, you need to get a Raspberry Pi with internet connectivity.
<li>The latest model (Raspberry Pi 3B) comes equipped with Wifi and ethernet</li>
<li>The Pi 0 also comes with Wifi, but is slower</li>
<li>Finally, you can also buy a Wifi adapter and plug it into any Raspberry Pi</li>

We recommend heading over to https://projects.raspberrypi.org for a quick tutorial on getting started.</p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[
        <p>To have an accurate estimate of the air quality in your area, you’ll need to buy sensors for the most common types of pollutants.
For an out-of-the-box solution, use the following sensors :
SDS011 : details
DHT22 : details
MQ2 : details
…
</p>
            <p>A minimal amount of coding is necessary if you wish to add differents sensors, but we’ll be glad to help at https://github.com/capteurPollutions/Embedded.
</p>
        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[
        <p>Please clone or download from github in your Raspberry Pi :

<li>mkdir ~/ClearSky</li>
<li>cd ~/ClearSky</li>
<li>git clone https://github.com/CapteursPollution/Embedded</li>
<li>cd Embedded/Installation/RaspberryPi/ &amp;&amp;  sudo sh setup.sh</li>
</p>
<p>After restarting, your Raspberry should now start reading the data from the sensors.</p>
    <p>Next up, configuring the mobile app to visualize this data !</p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[
<p>What’s the IP Address of the Raspberry Pi (How to get it ? ) : INPUT</p>
    <p>Help us spread knowledge and data about Air Quality ! We’re building a map of the data collected by our users and accessible to everyone (data is anonymized).</p>
<p>Do you wish to upload the data collected by your system : TOGGLE YES NO</p>
    <p>Optionally, you may want to use another server to upload your data to : INPUT SERVER ADD</p>
        ]]></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
